<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<component type="addon">
    <id>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.Plugins.DragonflyReverb</id>
    <extends>org.freedesktop.LinuxAudio.BaseExtension</extends>
    <name>DragonflyReverb</name>
    <summary>DragonflyReverb LV2/VST/VST3/CLAP</summary>
    <description>
      <p>Dragonfly Reverb is a bundle of free audio effect plugins (LV2, CLAP, VST and VST3).</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Dragonfly Hall Reverb is a free stereo-to-stereo reverb
        effect. It is primarily intended for use as a concert hall
        reverb. It also has numerous smaller presets representing
        rooms, studios, and chambers. It is based on Hibiki Reverb
        from Freeverb3VST, which uses Moorer's early reflection model
        and a modified FDN allpass Zita reverb.</li>
        <li>Dragonfly Room Reverb is a free stereo-to-stereo reverb
        effect. It has several different room presets, as well as a
        small number of hall presets and effect presets. It is based
        on ProG Reverb from Freeverb3VST, which uses Moorer's early
        reflection model and an implementation of Jon Dattorro's
        Progenitor Reverb algorithm.</li>
        <li>Dragonfly Plate is a free mono-to-stereo reverb plugin
        based on NVerb and STRev from Freeverb3 VST.</li>
        <li>Dragonfly Early Reflections is a free stereo-to-stereo
        reverb effect based on Moorer's early reflection model as
        implemented in Freeverb3 VST. This is the same algorithm used
        in Dragonfly Hall and Dragonfly Room, but without any late
        reverberation algorithm.</li>
      </ul>
    </description>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <update_contact>hub_AT_figuiere.net</update_contact>
    <url type="homepage">https://michaelwillis.github.io/dragonfly-reverb</url>
    <releases>
      <release date="2023-04-03" version="3.2.9">
        <description>
          <p>Disable denormals during all DSP</p>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2022-12-28" version="3.2.8">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fix bug in which setting predelay to zero does not
            update dsp predelay</li>
            <li>Update to latest DPF - fixes CLAP on Linux</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2022-09-25" version="3.2.7">
        <description>
          <p>Added CLAP plugin</p>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2022-03-31" version="3.2.6">
        <description>
          <p>Attempt at fixing bug on HiDPI displays and added VST3</p>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2021-03-04" version="3.2.5">
        <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Attempt to fix issue when mod is set to zero in Dragonfly Hall.</li>
            <li>Updated license to URI (to pass LV2 lint).</li>
            <li>Updated homepage URI.</li>
            <li>Fixed env var reference PKG_CONFIG in Makefiles.</li>
          </ul>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2020-12-07" version="3.2.3">
        <description>
          <p>Fix bug initializing dials and sliders that are set to
          zero upon loading the plugin.</p>
        </description>
      </release>
      <release date="2020-08-27" version="3.2.1" />
    </releases>
</component>
